[{"answer": "Well, I wouldn't say that, no.", "docId": "120308pmt", "aSentId": 45, "question": "But you've lost a bit of weight, haven't you, and buffed up a bit?", "qSentId": 44}, {"answer": "ANTORUM: Oh, I've got to tell you, I love it.", "docId": "120308pmt", "aSentId": 52, "question": "How are you finding the pace of it?", "qSentId": 51}, {"answer": "Well, I think most of the, quote, \"experts\" have looked at the fact, which is the states early on were fairly well stacked in his direction.", "docId": "120308pmt", "aSentId": 71, "question": "I mean, obviously, you're partly responsible, but why is he not getting, as he would see it, due credit for results?", "qSentId": 70}, {"answer": "Oh, yes, the snob comment did not go over very well.", "docId": "120308pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "Am I right on assuming that she rang you a few times that week?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "Well, well, I -- to be honest with you, I haven't really paid much attention to it.", "docId": "120308pmt", "aSentId": 124, "question": "Now that you've had time to reflect on what he said, do you want to go a little further?", "qSentId": 123}, {"answer": "He does not run the party.", "docId": "120308pmt", "aSentId": 136, "question": "He doesn't?", "qSentId": 135}, {"answer": "Well, of course not, no.", "docId": "120308pmt", "aSentId": 144, "question": "You'd view that as pretty offensive?", "qSentId": 143}, {"answer": "Well, this goes to the snob, snobbish, issue, which is, you know, he clearly did not tell the truth, that you don't necessarily go and, you know, accuse the person of -- on a personal level.", "docId": "120308pmt", "aSentId": 154, "question": "Is he a liar then?", "qSentId": 153}, {"answer": "Well, they've actually admitted, and inspectors have already certified, that they've -- you know, have a number of centrifuges, they're enriching uranium, far, far -- already far beyond what is necessary for nuclear power.", "docId": "120308pmt", "aSentId": 197, "question": "If America were to get involved in another military action based on a hunch or a premise that, you know, Ahmadinejad and his cohorts there did have nuclear weapons and it turned out they didn't, it would be another disaster, wouldn't it?", "qSentId": 196}, {"answer": "Turning to Syria, obviously, John McCain yesterday came out and said, quite stridently, it's time to launch airstrikes against the leadership there.", "docId": "120308pmt", "aSentId": 211, "question": "Now the question is, how far along are they?", "qSentId": 210}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, this is a related issue to Iran, because, you know, Syria is just a puppet state anymore of Iran.", "docId": "120308pmt", "aSentId": 214, "question": "Is it time that America got involved in some kind of military action?", "qSentId": 213}, {"answer": "Well, here's what I would say about this.", "docId": "120308pmt", "aSentId": 232, "question": "And I suppose my question for you would be, given the way that the gay marriage debate is going, gay rights debate is going, is it time that people, even if they have strong religious conviction on this issue, stop using inflammatory language to demean the gay community?", "qSentId": 231}, {"answer": "ANTORUM: You know, I hate to sound like I'm completely out of touch with what's going on in the popular culture, but I did not hear Kirk Cameron's remarks, so I don't know what he said.", "docId": "120308pmt", "aSentId": 242, "question": "Did you personally find anything Kirk Cameron said offensive?", "qSentId": 241}, {"answer": "It's a film, Piers.", "docId": "120308pmt", "aSentId": 266, "question": "I suppose the obvious question is, it's not really a film or a documentary, it's an election campaign promo, right?", "qSentId": 265}, {"answer": "Well, I think what the opportunity of this movie is, you know, we're used to looking at politicians and politics in a very small window.", "docId": "120308pmt", "aSentId": 271, "question": "What is the essence of this?", "qSentId": 270}, {"answer": "Well just because I live in L.A. doesn't mean I'm a sycophant.", "docId": "120308pmt", "aSentId": 280, "question": "But, you know, you've got to be careful as a filmmaker if you're making a thing like this but he doesn't come over as too everything Barack Obama touches is wonderful, haven't you?", "qSentId": 279}, {"answer": "Well, I mean the negative for me was there were too many accomplishments.", "docId": "120308pmt", "aSentId": 323, "question": "What are the negatives in your movie about Barack Obama?", "qSentId": 322}, {"answer": "That was the negative -- excuse me, that was the negative for me.", "docId": "120308pmt", "aSentId": 331, "question": "The only negativity about Barack Obama is there are too many positives?", "qSentId": 330}, {"answer": "I think there are negatives in the sense that the challenges, when you're trying to pass health care in a really toxic environment -- there are negatives in terms of the opposition he had, in terms of the political climate in Washington.", "docId": "120308pmt", "aSentId": 336, "question": "But are there any negatives in there?", "qSentId": 335}, {"answer": "I -- you know, I don't.", "docId": "120308pmt", "aSentId": 345, "question": "But where do you find fault in him, personally?", "qSentId": 344}, {"answer": "Well, no.", "docId": "120308pmt", "aSentId": 348, "question": "He's a perfect human being?", "qSentId": 347}, {"answer": "But, Piers, you haven't seen the movie.", "docId": "120308pmt", "aSentId": 355, "question": "I mean, are you dispassionate enough to do a Barack Obama video?", "qSentId": 354}, {"answer": "Well, I'll let the campaign tell you that.", "docId": "120308pmt", "aSentId": 362, "question": "How much did it cost and who paid?", "qSentId": 361}, {"answer": "Well, I still don't know if the whole world knows.", "docId": "120308pmt", "aSentId": 420, "question": "What is the next move for your organization?", "qSentId": 419}, {"answer": "I want to go for a billion.", "docId": "120308pmt", "aSentId": 427, "question": "Why not 200 million?", "qSentId": 426}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "120308pmt", "aSentId": 439, "question": "The question, really, I guess is what do you think can actually come of this in the next couple of months, say?", "qSentId": 438}, {"answer": "USSELL: Yes.", "docId": "120308pmt", "aSentId": 479, "question": "What can you say about that?", "qSentId": 478}, {"answer": "I say to anyone who is watching, go to the LRACrisisTracker.com -- LRACrisisTracker.com This is a real time website.", "docId": "120308pmt", "aSentId": 507, "question": "What do you say to that?", "qSentId": 506}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120308pmt", "aSentId": 537, "question": "And where do you take that part of the operation?", "qSentId": 536}]